Guide to the Records of the Office of the Director of Student Affairs, University Heights RG.12.1
New York University Archives
- Series III: Clubs and Societies
  - Chinese Students Society, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Circolo Italian (Italian Club), 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Clubs and Fraternities (Accredited), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Club Rosters, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Committee for Improved Education Values, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Commedia Dell'Arte, Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Conservative Coalition of NYU, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Constitutions of Inactive Groups, 1929-1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions of Inactive Groups, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Davidson Avenue Block Association, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Der Deutsche Verein, 1955-1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dormitory Committee, 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dormitories - Student Sit-In Demonstrations, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Draper Chemical Society, 1938-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - El Grito Borinqueno, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Action Group, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Living Experiment, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fairchild Sociological Society, 1961-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - French Club, 1960-1965 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Glee Club, 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Gould Hall Society, 1960-1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Heights Christian Association, 1961-1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Heights Daily News, 1967-1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Heights Dance Band, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Heights Equestrian Club, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Heights Festival Committee, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Heights Forensic Society, 1956-1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Heights Freaks and Perverts, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Heights Freedom Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Heights Graduate Student Council, 1960-1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Heights Interfaith Constitution, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Heights Photographic Society, 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Heights Symphony Orchestra, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Heights Young Democrats, 1961-1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Heights Young Republicans, 1948-1968 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Hilbert Math Society, 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Huntington Hill Historical Society, 1960-1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - In-Service Tutoring, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Interdormitory Council, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Aeronautical Science, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronical Engineers, 1962-1968 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Interfaith Council, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - International Student Center, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - International Student Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Cultural Foundation, 1964-1973 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Jeunesses - Musicales, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Karate Club, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Latin American Students Society, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Katara, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Loew Hall Society Judicial Committee, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Loew Hall Society, 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - John Marshall Pre-Law Society, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mensa, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Morse Mathematics and Physics Society, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Music Club, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Youth Alliance, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - New Fronts, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Newman Club, 1963-1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NYU Liberation Front, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - OASIS, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Olympia Houseplan, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Operation Abolition, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Operation Workshop, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Outdoor Club, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Palisades Handbook, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Perstare Magazine, 1960-1970 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Physiological Research Society, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Quadrangle, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sailing Club, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Sedgwick Hall, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Sedgwick Hall Judicial Committee, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Silver Hall Judiciary, 1969-1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Silver Hall Society, 1962-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ski Club, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Social Committee of Student Council, 1942-1955 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Society of American Military Engineers, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Society for Artsmen and Engineers, 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Society of Women Engineers, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Sports Car Club, 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Tau Beta Pi (Engineering), 1960-1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Team for Environmental Restoration and Rehabilitation through Action, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Athletic Organization, 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Engineering Council, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Veteran's Association/Undergraduate Engineering Council, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Violet, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Violet, 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Violet Questionnaire, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - West Indian Association, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Young People's Socialist League, Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - WNYU, 1963-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Fraternities and Sororities
  - Fraternities Forms, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities General Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Fraternities Housing, Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fraternities Inspection and Safety Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fraternities Pledge Lists, 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fraternities - Scholastic Standings, 1960-1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities Washington Square, 1958-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fraternity Evaluation Conference, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Fraternity Operations Seminar, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Interfraternity Council Constitution Survey, 1934-1937 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - IFC Constitutions and Revisions, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - IFC General Correspondence, 1957-1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - IFC Judicial Committee, 1958-1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - IFC Minutes, 1934-1944 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - IFC Minutes, 1945-1955 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - IFC Minutes, 1956-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - IFC National Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - IFC President Files, 1957-1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - National Panhellenic Conference Forms, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - National Panhellenic Conference: Manual of Information, 1958, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - NYU Heights Panhellenic: Constitution and By-Laws, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - NYU Heights Panhellenic: Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - NYU Heights Panhellenic Rushing Rules, Undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority, 1961-1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Delta Phi Epsilon, 1961-1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Pi Omicron Phi Sorority, 1959-1968 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi Pledge List and Rosters, 1955-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Phi Omega Fraternity Correspondence and Constitution, 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Phi Omega Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Beta Alpha Kappa Fraternity, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Delta Phi Fraternity, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Gamma Pi Delta Fraternity, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Kappa Sigma Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Kappa Sigma Fraternity Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1960-1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Phi Sigma Delta Fraternity Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Phi Sigma Delta Fraternity Pledge Lists and Roseters, 1959-1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Pi Lamda Phi Fraternity Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Pi Lamda Phi Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1959-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Psi Upsilon Fraternity, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu Fraternity, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Tau Delta Phi Fraternity Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1959-1969 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Tau Delta Phi Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1962-1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi Fraternity Correspondence, 1960-1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Zeta Beta Tau Correspondence, 1962-1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Zeta Beta Tau Fraternity Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Zeta Beta Tau Fraternity Pledge Lists and Rosters, 1959-1971 (Box 30, Folder 10)